{
    "doubleJeopardy": [
        {
            "category_name": "Solar System", 
            "category_number": "category1", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Neptune", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "This panet is the coolest in our solar system.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Uranus", 
                        "Pluto", 
                        "Saturn", 
                        "Jupiter", 
                        "Mercury", 
                        "Venus", 
                        "Sun", 
                        "Mars", 
                        "Earth", 
                        "Moon", 
                        "Triton", 
                        "Ceres", 
                        "Milky Way", 
                        "Eris", 
                        "Titan"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Earth", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "This planet is three quarters covered by water.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Mars", 
                        "Venus", 
                        "Sun", 
                        "Moon", 
                        "Mercury", 
                        "Jupiter", 
                        "Saturn", 
                        "Pluto", 
                        "Neptune", 
                        "Uranus", 
                        "Titan", 
                        "Europa", 
                        "Sirius", 
                        "Ceres"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Mercury", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "This is the smallest planet in our solar system.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Venus", 
                        "Jupiter", 
                        "Saturn", 
                        "Mars", 
                        "Uranus", 
                        "Neptune", 
                        "Sun", 
                        "Pluto", 
                        "Solar System", 
                        "Earth", 
                        "Moon", 
                        "Ceres", 
                        "Milky Way", 
                        "Titan", 
                        "Ganymede", 
                        "Eris", 
                        "2060 Chiron", 
                        "Europa", 
                        "Makemake", 
                        "Callisto", 
                        "Io", 
                        "Phobos", 
                        "Enceladus", 
                        "Asteroid belt"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Venus", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "This planet is the hottest in our solar system.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Uranus", 
                        "Pluto", 
                        "Saturn", 
                        "Jupiter", 
                        "Mercury", 
                        "Venus", 
                        "Sun", 
                        "Mars", 
                        "Earth", 
                        "Moon"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Neptune", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "This planet is the farthest from our sun in our solar system.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Uranus", 
                        "Pluto", 
                        "Saturn", 
                        "Jupiter", 
                        "Mercury", 
                        "Venus", 
                        "Sun", 
                        "Solar System", 
                        "Mars", 
                        "Earth", 
                        "Moon", 
                        "Triton", 
                        "Ceres", 
                        "Milky Way", 
                        "Eris", 
                        "2060 Chiron", 
                        "Titan", 
                        "Asteroid belt", 
                        "S/2004 N 1", 
                        "Makemake", 
                        "Europa", 
                        "Laomedeia", 
                        "Ganymede", 
                        "Charon"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }
    ], 
    "singleJeopardy": [
        {
            "category_name": "Potent Potables", 
            "category_number": "category1", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Juniper", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "Gin derives its distinguishing flavor from this type of berry.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Vodka", 
                        "Triple sec", 
                        "Tequila", 
                        "Cosmopolitan", 
                        "Iced tea", 
                        "Daiquiri", 
                        "Cuba Libre", 
                        "Mai Tai", 
                        "Mojito", 
                        "Margarita", 
                        "Tequila Sunrise", 
                        "Bloody Mary", 
                        "Martini", 
                        "Manhattan", 
                        "White Russian", 
                        "Sour", 
                        "Black Russian", 
                        "Grenadine", 
                        "Blue Lagoon", 
                        "Negroni", 
                        "Caipirinha"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Guinness", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "St James Gate Brewery, home to this beer, was originally leased to its creator for 45 Irish Pounds per year for 9,000 years.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Stout", 
                        "Beer", 
                        "Ale", 
                        "Lager", 
                        "Draught beer", 
                        "Pilsner", 
                        "Porter", 
                        "India pale ale", 
                        "Whisky", 
                        "Malt", 
                        "Cider", 
                        "Irish Car Bomb", 
                        "Wheat beer", 
                        "Hops", 
                        "Schwarzbier", 
                        "Vodka", 
                        "Distilled beverage", 
                        "Barley", 
                        "Tequila", 
                        "Irish stew", 
                        "Rum", 
                        "Bourbon whiskey", 
                        "Martini"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Manhattan", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "Named after a New York borough, this drink is traditionally made with rye whiskey, bitters, and sweet vermouth.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "New York City", 
                        "New York", 
                        "United States of America", 
                        "Brooklyn", 
                        "Central Park", 
                        "The Bronx", 
                        "Queens", 
                        "Empire State Building", 
                        "Upper East Side", 
                        "Harlem", 
                        "SoHo, Manhattan", 
                        "Lower Manhattan", 
                        "Staten Island", 
                        "Times Square", 
                        "Upper West Side", 
                        "Chelsea", 
                        "Long Island", 
                        "New Jersey", 
                        "Theatre District", 
                        "Greenwich Village", 
                        "Statue of Liberty"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Long Island Iced Tea", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "A mixture of gin, vodka, rum, tequila, sweet and sour, and Coke, this drink does not actually contain the beverage listed in its name.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Vodka", 
                        "Triple sec", 
                        "Tequila", 
                        "Cosmopolitan", 
                        "Iced tea", 
                        "Daiquiri", 
                        "Cuba Libre", 
                        "Mai Tai", 
                        "Mojito", 
                        "Margarita", 
                        "Tequila Sunrise", 
                        "Bloody Mary", 
                        "Martini", 
                        "Manhattan", 
                        "White Russian", 
                        "Sour", 
                        "Black Russian", 
                        "Grenadine", 
                        "Blue Lagoon", 
                        "Negroni", 
                        "Caipirinha"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Champagne", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "Containing roughly 49 million bubbles, the pressure in a bottle of this beverage is approximately 90 pounds per square inch.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Wine", 
                        "Sparkling wine", 
                        "Whisky", 
                        "Prosecco", 
                        "Red Wine", 
                        "White wine", 
                        "Vodka", 
                        "Beer", 
                        "Cognac", 
                        "Grape", 
                        "Liqueur", 
                        "Water", 
                        "Rum", 
                        "Mimosa", 
                        "Gin", 
                        "Tequila", 
                        "Dessert", 
                        "Brandy", 
                        "Chocolate", 
                        "Cider", 
                        "Juice", 
                        "Cheese"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "category_name": "Sports Teams", 
            "category_number": "category3", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Real Madrid F.C.", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "Led by Christano Ronaldo, this Spanish football team won the UEFA Champions League tournament in 2017.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "FC Barcelona", 
                        "Manchester United F.C.", 
                        "Juventus F.C.", 
                        "Chelsea F.C.", 
                        "Arsenal F.C.", 
                        "FC Bayern Munich", 
                        "Manchester City F.C.", 
                        "Paris Saint-Germain F.C.", 
                        "A.C. Milan", 
                        "Atl\u00e9tico Madrid", 
                        "Liverpool F.C.", 
                        "Portugal national football team", 
                        "Clube de Regatas do Flamengo", 
                        "Inter Milan", 
                        "Borussia Dortmund", 
                        "Persib Bandung", 
                        "Olympique de Marseille", 
                        "Sport Club Corinthians Paulista", 
                        "Al Ahly SC", 
                        "Sociedade Esportiva Palmeiras", 
                        "Tottenham Hotspur F.C.", 
                        "AS Monaco FC", 
                        "Zamalek SC", 
                        "Olympique Lyonnais"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "San Antonio Spurs", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "Boasting players such as Tim Duncan and Manu Ginobili, this NBA franchise has the highest all time winning percentage in the NBA.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Cleveland Cavaliers", 
                        "Golden State Warriors", 
                        "Oklahoma City Thunder", 
                        "Los Angeles Lakers", 
                        "Houston Rockets", 
                        "Boston Celtics", 
                        "Chicago Bulls", 
                        "Los Angeles Clippers", 
                        "Miami Heat", 
                        "New York Knicks", 
                        "Dallas Mavericks", 
                        "Toronto Raptors", 
                        "Philadelphia 76ers", 
                        "Portland Trail Blazers", 
                        "Indiana Pacers", 
                        "Brooklyn Nets", 
                        "Atlanta Hawks", 
                        "Memphis Grizzlies", 
                        "Detroit Pistons", 
                        "New Orleans Pelicans", 
                        "Washington Wizards", 
                        "Minnesota Timberwolves", 
                        "Phoenix Suns", 
                        "Charlotte Hornets"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Chicago Cubs", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "Breaking the \u201cCurse of the Billy Goat,\u201d this national league baseball team won the World Series in 2016.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Chicago White Sox", 
                        "St. Louis Cardinals", 
                        "Milwaukee Brewers", 
                        "New York Yankees", 
                        "Los Angeles Dodgers", 
                        "Cleveland Indians", 
                        "Cincinnati Reds", 
                        "New York Mets", 
                        "Pittsburgh Pirates", 
                        "Houston Astros", 
                        "San Francisco Giants", 
                        "Colorado Rockies", 
                        "Atlanta Braves", 
                        "Kansas City Royals", 
                        "Washington Nationals", 
                        "Miami Marlins", 
                        "Boston Red Sox", 
                        "Detroit Tigers", 
                        "Minnesota Twins", 
                        "Arizona Diamondbacks", 
                        "Texas Rangers", 
                        "Baltimore Orioles", 
                        "Los Angeles Angels of Anaheim", 
                        "Philadelphia Phillies"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Edmonton Oilers", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "Widely considered the greatest hockey player of all time, Wayne Gretsky began his career in Edmonton, playing for this team.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Calgary Flames", 
                        "Montreal Canadiens", 
                        "Vancouver Canucks", 
                        "Toronto Maple Leafs", 
                        "Pittsburgh Penguins", 
                        "Chicago Blackhawks", 
                        "Boston Bruins", 
                        "New York Rangers", 
                        "New York Islanders", 
                        "Winnipeg Jets", 
                        "Los Angeles Kings", 
                        "Anaheim Ducks", 
                        "Nashville Predators", 
                        "San Jose Sharks", 
                        "Detroit Red Wings", 
                        "Ottawa Senators", 
                        "Philadelphia Flyers", 
                        "New Jersey Devils", 
                        "Buffalo Sabres", 
                        "St. Louis Blues", 
                        "Columbus Blue Jackets", 
                        "Washington Capitals", 
                        "Colorado Avalanche", 
                        "Tampa Bay Lightning"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Oakland Raiders", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "This NFL team plans to relocate to Las Vegas, Nevada in 2019.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Denver Broncos", 
                        "San Francisco 49ers", 
                        "New England Patriots", 
                        "Los Angeles Chargers", 
                        "Seattle Seahawks", 
                        "Dallas Cowboys", 
                        "Los Angeles Rams", 
                        "Green Bay Packers", 
                        "Houston Texans", 
                        "Kansas City Chiefs", 
                        "New York Giants", 
                        "Pittsburgh Steelers", 
                        "Philadelphia Eagles", 
                        "Carolina Panthers", 
                        "Baltimore Ravens", 
                        "Minnesota Vikings", 
                        "Cleveland Browns", 
                        "Detroit Lions", 
                        "Atlanta Falcons", 
                        "Indianapolis Colts", 
                        "New York Jets", 
                        "Washington Redskins", 
                        "New Orleans Saints", 
                        "Tampa Bay Buccaneers"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "category_name": "Periodic Table", 
            "category_number": "category2", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Mercury", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "This metal is liquid at room temperature.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Venus", 
                        "Jupiter", 
                        "Saturn", 
                        "Mars", 
                        "Uranus", 
                        "Neptune", 
                        "Sun", 
                        "Pluto", 
                        "Solar System", 
                        "Earth", 
                        "Moon", 
                        "Ceres", 
                        "Milky Way", 
                        "Titan", 
                        "Ganymede", 
                        "Eris", 
                        "2060 Chiron", 
                        "Europa", 
                        "Makemake", 
                        "Callisto", 
                        "Io", 
                        "Phobos", 
                        "Enceladus", 
                        "Asteroid belt"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Uranium", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "The 235 isotope of this element is used to generate energy for nuclear power plants.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Plutonium", 
                        "Metal", 
                        "Thorium", 
                        "Radium", 
                        "Lead", 
                        "Coal", 
                        "Polonium", 
                        "Neptunium", 
                        "Hydrogen", 
                        "Carbon", 
                        "Mercury", 
                        "Titanium", 
                        "Tungsten", 
                        "Cobalt", 
                        "Protactinium", 
                        "Caesium", 
                        "Arsenic"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Neon", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "This gas is used extensively in exterior lighting, and not just in Las Vegas.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Argon", 
                        "Krypton", 
                        "Xenon", 
                        "Oxygen", 
                        "Hydrogen", 
                        "Chlorine", 
                        "Boron", 
                        "Bromine", 
                        "Silicon", 
                        "Mercury", 
                        "Beryllium", 
                        "Carbon", 
                        "Lithium"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Silver", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "Upon discovery of the Comstock Load in 1859, people flocked to Nevada to mine for this metal, abbreviated Ag.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Gold", 
                        "Zinc", 
                        "Copper", 
                        "Aluminium", 
                        "Iron", 
                        "Boron", 
                        "Bromine", 
                        "Silicon", 
                        "Mercury", 
                        "Beryllium", 
                        "Carbon"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Potassium", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "Abbreviated K, this element can be found in bananas and helps reduce the occurrence of muscle cramps.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Sodium", 
                        "Magnesium", 
                        "Iron", 
                        "Calcium", 
                        "Phosphorus", 
                        "Boron", 
                        "Bromine", 
                        "Silicon", 
                        "Mercury", 
                        "Beryllium", 
                        "Carbon"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "category_name": "Famous Inventor Quotes", 
            "category_number": "category5", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Steve Jobs", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "This quote was said by a famous inventor, \u201cStay hungry, stay foolish.\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Bill Gates", 
                        "Steve Wozniak", 
                        "Laurene Powell", 
                        "Lisa Brennan-Jobs", 
                        "Tim Cook", 
                        "Mark Zuckerberg", 
                        "Steven Spielberg", 
                        "Ronald Wayne", 
                        "Chrisann Brennan", 
                        "Abdulfattah John Jandali", 
                        "John Sculley", 
                        "Elon Musk", 
                        "Larry Page", 
                        "Warren Buffett", 
                        "Jonathan Ive", 
                        "Mona Simpson", 
                        "Tim Berners-Lee", 
                        "Melinda Gates", 
                        "Albert Einstein", 
                        "Jeff Bezos", 
                        "Scott Forstall", 
                        "Richard Branson", 
                        "Stephen Hawking"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Abert Einstein", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "This quote was said by a famous inventor, \u201cCreativity is intelligence having fun.\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Elsa Einstein", 
                        "Eduard Einstein", 
                        "Isaac Newton", 
                        "Hans Albert Einstein", 
                        "Lieserl Einstein", 
                        "Marie Curie", 
                        "Max Planck", 
                        "Nikola Tesla", 
                        "Werner Heisenberg", 
                        "Galileo Galilei", 
                        "Stephen Hawking", 
                        "Thomas Edison", 
                        "Niels Bohr", 
                        "Charles Darwin", 
                        "Sigmund Freud", 
                        "Leonardo da Vinci", 
                        "Adolf Hitler", 
                        "Bernhard Caesar Einstein", 
                        "Alexander Graham Bell", 
                        "Marilyn Monroe", 
                        "Mahatma Gandhi", 
                        "Steve Jobs"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Henry Ford", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "This quote was said by a famous inventor, \u201cIf I had asked people what they wanted, they would have said faster horses.\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Gerald Ford", 
                        "Thomas Edison", 
                        "Charles Lindbergh", 
                        "Edsel Ford", 
                        "Frederick Winslow Taylor", 
                        "Karl Benz", 
                        "Clara Ala Bryant", 
                        "William Clay Ford Jr.", 
                        "Andrew Carnegie", 
                        "John D. Rockefeller", 
                        "Henri Fayol", 
                        "Mark Fields", 
                        "Alexander Graham Bell", 
                        "Bill Gates", 
                        "Edsel Ford II", 
                        "Steve Jobs", 
                        "Henry Ford II", 
                        "Albert Einstein", 
                        "William Ford", 
                        "Dale Carnegie", 
                        "Nikola Tesla", 
                        "Napoleon Hill", 
                        "William Clay Ford Sr.", 
                        "Gottlieb Daimler"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Thomas Edison", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "This quote was said by a famous inventor, \u201cI have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work.\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Nikola Tesla", 
                        "Alexander Graham Bell", 
                        "Albert Einstein", 
                        "Henry Ford", 
                        "Charles Edison", 
                        "Joseph Swan", 
                        "Isaac Newton", 
                        "Benjamin Franklin", 
                        "Michael Faraday", 
                        "Theodore Miller Edison", 
                        "George Westinghouse", 
                        "Hiram Maxim", 
                        "Galileo Galilei", 
                        "Thomas Jefferson", 
                        "Mina Miller", 
                        "Marie Curie", 
                        "Louis Pasteur", 
                        "Mary Stilwell", 
                        "Leonardo da Vinci", 
                        "Stephen Hawking", 
                        "Nancy Matthews Elliott", 
                        "Charles Darwin", 
                        "Emile Berliner", 
                        "Guglielmo Marconi"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Nikola Tesla", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "This quote was said by a famous inventor, \u201cThe present is theirs; the future, for which I really worked, is mine.\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Thomas Edison", 
                        "Albert Einstein", 
                        "Elon Musk", 
                        "Michael Faraday", 
                        "Isaac Newton", 
                        "Alexander Graham Bell", 
                        "Guglielmo Marconi", 
                        "George Westinghouse", 
                        "Marie Curie", 
                        "Stephen Hawking", 
                        "Galileo Galilei", 
                        "Leonardo da Vinci", 
                        "Heinrich Hertz", 
                        "Charles Darwin", 
                        "James Clerk Maxwell", 
                        "Milutin Tesla", 
                        "Mark Twain", 
                        "Walter Russell", 
                        "Alessandro Volta", 
                        "Benjamin Franklin", 
                        "Nicolaus Copernicus", 
                        "Louis Pasteur", 
                        "J. P. Morgan"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "category_name": "TV Trivia", 
            "category_number": "category4", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Star Trek", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "The first interracial kiss on American Network Television was aired on this sci-fi series in 1968.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Lost in Space", 
                        "Battlestar Galactica", 
                        "Babylon 5", 
                        "The Outer Limits", 
                        "Andromeda", 
                        "Doctor Who", 
                        "Firefly", 
                        "Mission Impossible", 
                        "Stargate Universe", 
                        "Futurama"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "I Love Lucy", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "Starring Lucille Ball and Desi Arnaz, this tv show was voted the \u201cBest TV Show of all Time\u201d in a poll done by ABC News.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "The Lucy Show", 
                        "The Lucy-Desi Comedy Hour", 
                        "Here's Lucy", 
                        "The Andy Griffith Show", 
                        "Our MIss Brooks", 
                        "My Little Margie", 
                        "The Danny Thomas Show", 
                        "The Honeymooners", 
                        "The Real McCoys"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "The Simpsons", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "The longest running animated series in US history is this show, having aired over 500 episodes.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Family Guy", 
                        "Futurama", 
                        "South Park", 
                        "American Dad", 
                        "The Cleveland Show"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Larry King", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "This talk show host headlined a late night show on CNN from 1985-2010, winning two Peabody Awards and 10 Cable ACE Awards.", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Johnny Carson", 
                        "Shawn King", 
                        "Steven Spielberg", 
                        "David Letterman", 
                        "O. J. Simpson", 
                        "Danny Southwick", 
                        "Jacque Fresco", 
                        "Larry David", 
                        "Piers Morgan", 
                        "Regis Philbin", 
                        "Jay Leno", 
                        "Anderson Cooper", 
                        "Jerry Seinfeld", 
                        "Howard Stern", 
                        "Zsa Zsa G\u00e1bor", 
                        "Kathy Griffin", 
                        "Bill Maher", 
                        "Craig Ferguson", 
                        "Oprah Winfrey", 
                        "Barbara Walters", 
                        "Ray Liotta"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Game of Thrones", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "This HBO show is an adaptation of George R.R. Martin\u2019s novel series titled \u201cA Song of Ice and Fire.\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Westworld", 
                        "The Sopranos", 
                        "The Wire", 
                        "Veep", 
                        "Silicon Vallye", 
                        "True Blood", 
                        "Deadwood", 
                        "Boardwalk Empire", 
                        "Girls", 
                        "Sex and the City"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "category_name": "Superheros", 
            "category_number": "category7", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Wonder Woman", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "This Amazonian woman can make you tell the truth with the lasso of truth", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Poision Ivy", 
                        "Batgirl", 
                        "Catwoman", 
                        "Hearly Quinn", 
                        "Superwoman", 
                        "Supergirl", 
                        "Power Girl"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Hulk", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "You better not make this green monster angry", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Iron Man", 
                        "Spider-Man", 
                        "Captain America", 
                        "Thor", 
                        "Superman", 
                        "Black Widow", 
                        "Batman", 
                        "Wolverine", 
                        "Clint Barton", 
                        "Ultron", 
                        "Deadpool", 
                        "Loki", 
                        "Venom", 
                        "She-Hulk", 
                        "Joker", 
                        "Daredevil", 
                        "Betty Ross", 
                        "Doctor Strange", 
                        "Thunderbolt Ross", 
                        "Thanos", 
                        "Diana Prince", 
                        "Wanda Maximoff", 
                        "Nick Fury", 
                        "Black Panther"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Iron Man", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "This man of metal from Marvel is known for his high tech suit", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Hulk", 
                        "Spider-Man", 
                        "Thor", 
                        "Ultron", 
                        "Black Widow", 
                        "Superman", 
                        "Captain America", 
                        "Wolverine", 
                        "Batman"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Joker", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "This clown is known for asking \u201cWhy so serious?\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Harley Quinn", 
                        "Batman", 
                        "Superman", 
                        "Robin", 
                        "Catwoman", 
                        "Riddler", 
                        "Deadshot", 
                        "Spider-Man", 
                        "Two-Face", 
                        "Bane", 
                        "Batgirl", 
                        "Diana Prince", 
                        "Nightwing", 
                        "Poison Ivy", 
                        "Penguin", 
                        "Hulk", 
                        "Red Hood", 
                        "Killer Croc", 
                        "Flash", 
                        "Lex Luthor", 
                        "Iron Man", 
                        "Deadpool", 
                        "Enchantress", 
                        "Deathstroke"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Batman", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "This dark knight is based in Gotham City", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Superman", 
                        "Joker", 
                        "Spider-Man", 
                        "Catwoman", 
                        "Diana Prince", 
                        "Harley Quinn", 
                        "Iron Man", 
                        "Robin", 
                        "Flash", 
                        "Nightwing", 
                        "Batgirl", 
                        "Hulk", 
                        "Captain America", 
                        "Green Lantern", 
                        "Aquaman", 
                        "Bane", 
                        "Poison Ivy", 
                        "Riddler", 
                        "Deathstroke", 
                        "Deadpool", 
                        "Wolverine", 
                        "Two-Face", 
                        "Talia al Ghul", 
                        "Damian Wayne"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "category_name": "Company Slogan", 
            "category_number": "category6", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Lay's", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "This company slogan is, \u201cBetcha Can't Eat Just One\u201d ", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Ritz", 
                        "Doritos", 
                        "Fritos", 
                        "Wheat Thins", 
                        "Tostitos", 
                        "Cheetos", 
                        "Pringles", 
                        "Triscuit", 
                        "Hostess"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "BMW", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "This company slogan is, \u201cThe Ultimate Driving Machine\u201d ", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Mercedes-Benz", 
                        "Lexus", 
                        "Audi", 
                        "Jaguar Cars", 
                        "Infiniti", 
                        "Volkswagen", 
                        "Mazda Motor Corporation", 
                        "Honda Motor Company", 
                        "Tesla, Inc.", 
                        "Land Rover", 
                        "Lamborghini", 
                        "Alfa Romeo", 
                        "Nissan", 
                        "Ford Motor Company", 
                        "Ducati", 
                        "Ferrari S.p.A.", 
                        "Porsche", 
                        "Toyota", 
                        "AB Volvo", 
                        "Harley-Davidson", 
                        "Chevrolet", 
                        "Kia Motors", 
                        "Maserati", 
                        "Bentley Motors Limited"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Nike", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "This company slogan is, \u201cJust do it\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Adidas", 
                        "Under Armor", 
                        "Reebok", 
                        "ASICS", 
                        "New Balance", 
                        "Puma", 
                        "Vans", 
                        "Skechers", 
                        "Fitbit", 
                        "Foot Locker"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "MasterCard", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "This company slogan is, \u201cThere are some things money can't buy. For everything else, there's MasterCard.\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Visa", 
                        "American Express", 
                        "Capital One", 
                        "Barclaycard", 
                        "PayPal", 
                        "Diners Club International", 
                        "JCB Co., Ltd.", 
                        "Walmart", 
                        "Sears", 
                        "Citibank", 
                        "Payoneer", 
                        "Skrill", 
                        "Nike", 
                        "WebMoney", 
                        "Bank of America", 
                        "Western Union", 
                        "Neteller", 
                        "Stripe", 
                        "Bank of Montreal", 
                        "Banco Bradesco", 
                        "China UnionPay", 
                        "HSBC", 
                        "Sberbank of Russia", 
                        "Banco do Brasil"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Apple", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "This company slogan is, \u201cThink Different\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Federal Bureau of Investigation", 
                        "Google", 
                        "Microsoft Corporation", 
                        "Samsung Group", 
                        "Dell", 
                        "Best Buy", 
                        "Hewlett-Packard", 
                        "Fitbit", 
                        "Amazon.com, Inc.", 
                        "Nokia", 
                        "Lenovo", 
                        "Asus", 
                        "IBM", 
                        "Sony Corporation", 
                        "Mophie", 
                        "HTC", 
                        "Intel", 
                        "Huawei", 
                        "AT&T", 
                        "Tesla, Inc.", 
                        "Alienware", 
                        "Xiaomi", 
                        "Verizon Wireless", 
                        "Federal government of the United States"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "category_name": "History", 
            "category_number": "category9", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Martin Luther King Jr", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "This man made a famous speech titled \u201cI have a dream\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Malcolm X", 
                        "Rosa Parks", 
                        "Mahatma Gandhi", 
                        "Nelson Mandela", 
                        "Coretta Scott King", 
                        "John F. Kennedy", 
                        "Martin Luther King III", 
                        "Martin Luther", 
                        "Barack Obama", 
                        "Abraham Lincoln", 
                        "Mother Teresa", 
                        "Lyndon B. Johnson", 
                        "James Earl Ray", 
                        "Bernice King", 
                        "Yolanda King", 
                        "Dexter Scott King", 
                        "Martin Luther King Sr.", 
                        "Anne Frank", 
                        "Robert F. Kennedy", 
                        "Jesse Jackson", 
                        "James Baldwin", 
                        "Malala Yousafzai", 
                        "Adolf Hitler", 
                        "Muhammad Ali"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "World War I", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "This war was known as \u201cThe Great War\u201d", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "World War II", 
                        "Cold War", 
                        "American Civil War", 
                        "Battle of the Somme", 
                        "Vietnam War", 
                        "Battle of Verdun", 
                        "Gallipoli Campaign", 
                        "Attack on Pearl Harbor", 
                        "Korean War", 
                        "Russo-Japanese War", 
                        "Spanish Civil War", 
                        "Atomic bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki", 
                        "Normandy landings", 
                        "Russian Civil War", 
                        "Balkan Wars", 
                        "First Battle of the Marne", 
                        "October Revolution", 
                        "Battle of Vimy Ridge", 
                        "American Revolutionary War", 
                        "Franco-Prussian War", 
                        "Russian Revolution", 
                        "Gulf War", 
                        "Crimean War", 
                        "Napoleonic Wars"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "George Washington", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "This man was the first president of the USA", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Gerald Ford", 
                        "Benedict Arnold", 
                        "Thomas Jefferson", 
                        "Abraham Lincoln", 
                        "John Adams", 
                        "Jimmy Carter", 
                        "Martha Washington", 
                        "Benjamin Franklin", 
                        "Alexander Hamilton", 
                        "James Madison", 
                        "Theodore Roosevelt", 
                        "Andrew Jackson", 
                        "James Monroe", 
                        "John F. Kennedy", 
                        "Franklin D. Roosevelt", 
                        "Barack Obama", 
                        "John Quincy Adams", 
                        "Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette", 
                        "George W. Bush", 
                        "Martin Van Buren", 
                        "Ulysses S. Grant", 
                        "Robert E. Lee", 
                        "Patrick Henry"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Plymouth", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "The pilgrims landed on this rock when they first came to America", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Boston", 
                        "Duxbury", 
                        "Jamestown", 
                        "Quincy", 
                        "Carver", 
                        "Wareham", 
                        "Falmouth", 
                        "Salem", 
                        "Marshfield", 
                        "Hyannis", 
                        "Sandwich", 
                        "Weymouth", 
                        "New Bedford", 
                        "Taunton", 
                        "Provincetown", 
                        "Middleborough", 
                        "Braintree", 
                        "Worcester", 
                        "Hingham", 
                        "Barnstable", 
                        "Bourne", 
                        "Framingham", 
                        "Manomet", 
                        "Cambridge"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Louisiana Purchase", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "This purchase from the French in 1803 doubles the size of the United States", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "West Florida", 
                        "Red River", 
                        "Gadsden Purchase", 
                        "Florida", 
                        "Texas", 
                        "Alaska", 
                        "Virgin Islands", 
                        "Mariana Islands", 
                        "Caroline Islands", 
                        "Marshall Islands"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "category_name": "Food and Drink", 
            "category_number": "category8", 
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answer": "Chicken", 
                    "number": "question5", 
                    "question": "This meat is the leading source of salmonella poisoning", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Pork", 
                        "Turkey", 
                        "Steak", 
                        "Lamb", 
                        "Brisket", 
                        "Sausage", 
                        "Tomato"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Flambe", 
                    "number": "question4", 
                    "question": "This cooking procedure includes adding alchohol to a hot pan to create flames", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Grill", 
                        "Pan-Fry", 
                        "Deep-Fry", 
                        "Boil", 
                        "Roast", 
                        "Bake", 
                        "Sear", 
                        "Poach", 
                        "Simmer", 
                        "Broil", 
                        "Steam"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Wine", 
                    "number": "question1", 
                    "question": "Jesus was said to turn water into this", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Red Wine", 
                        "Beer", 
                        "White wine", 
                        "Grape", 
                        "Sparkling wine", 
                        "Whisky", 
                        "Distilled beverage", 
                        "Pinot noir", 
                        "Chardonnay", 
                        "Cabernet Sauvignon", 
                        "Vodka", 
                        "Cheese", 
                        "Merlot", 
                        "Fruit", 
                        "Liqueur", 
                        "Coffee", 
                        "Bread", 
                        "Meat", 
                        "Dessert", 
                        "Rum", 
                        "Juice", 
                        "Chocolate", 
                        "Brandy"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "Trix", 
                    "number": "question3", 
                    "question": "This cereal is only for kids, no silly rabbits!", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Honey Nut Cheerios", 
                        "Frosted Flakes", 
                        "Honey Bunches of Oats", 
                        "Cinnamon Toast Crunch", 
                        "Special K", 
                        "Frosted Mini Wheats", 
                        "Lucky Charms", 
                        "Froot Loops", 
                        "Raisin Bran", 
                        "Waffle Crips", 
                        "Corn Flakes", 
                        "Corn Pops"
                    ]
                }, 
                {
                    "answer": "hamburger", 
                    "number": "question2", 
                    "question": "Mcdonalds sells 75 of these every second", 
                    "wrong_answers": [
                        "Pizza", 
                        "French fries", 
                        "Sandwich", 
                        "Hot dog", 
                        "Fast food", 
                        "Cheeseburger", 
                        "Chicken meat", 
                        "Cheese", 
                        "Steak", 
                        "Bread", 
                        "Meat", 
                        "Beef", 
                        "Dessert", 
                        "Onion", 
                        "Sushi", 
                        "Tomato", 
                        "Cuisine of the United States", 
                        "Patty", 
                        "Potato", 
                        "Taco", 
                        "Kebab", 
                        "Bun", 
                        "Fish as food", 
                        "Lettuce"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}